[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Kot",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["dog", "cat", "bird"],
        "correctanswer": "cat",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Dzień Dobry",
        "type": "writting",
        "correctanswer": "Good Morning",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Dom",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["house", "car", "tree"],
        "correctanswer": "house",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Jabłko",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["banana", "apple", "grape"],
        "correctanswer": "apple",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Dobranoc",
        "type": "writting",
        "correctanswer": "Good Night",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Czy możesz mi pomóc?",
        "type": "writting",
        "correctanswer": "Can you help me?",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Pies",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["dog", "cat", "mouse"],
        "correctanswer": "dog",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Książka",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["book", "pen", "paper"],
        "correctanswer": "book",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Zielony",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["red", "green", "blue"],
        "correctanswer": "green",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Dziękuję",
        "type": "writting",
        "correctanswer": "Thank you",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Proszę",
        "type": "writting",
        "correctanswer": "Please",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Rzeka",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["lake", "river", "sea"],
        "correctanswer": "river",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Woda",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["water", "juice", "milk"],
        "correctanswer": "water",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Dziecko",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["child", "parent", "teacher"],
        "correctanswer": "child",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Gdzie jest toaleta?",
        "type": "writting",
        "correctanswer": "Where is the toilet?",
        "category": "Grammar"
    }
]
